Chaos loves company.
Borderlands is a action, science fiction, comedy film directed by Eli Roth.
Returning to her home planet, an infamous bounty hunter forms an
unexpected alliance with a team of unlikely heroes.
Together, they battle monsters and dangerous bandits to protect a
young girl who holds the key to unimaginable power.
Lilith, played by Cate Blanchett.
Roland, played by Kevin Hart.
Atlas, played by Edgar Ramírez.
Tannis, played by Jamie Lee Curtis.
Tiny Tina, played by Ariana Greenblatt.
Krieg, played by Florian Munteanu.
Borderlands is a 2024 American science fiction comedy film directed and
co-written by Eli Roth, based on the video game series.
Cate Blanchett stars as Lillith, an outlaw who forms an alliance with a team of misfits
to find the missing daughter of the most powerful man in the universe.
The ensemble cast also features Kevin Hart, Jack Black, Edgar Ramirez, Ariana
Greenblatt, Florian Munteanu, Gina Gershon, and Jamie Lee Curtis.
The film was announced in August 2015, with Leigh Whannell in talks to direct.
By February 2020, Roth was attached to direct from a screenplay by Craig Mazin.
Casting took place from May 2020 to April 2021, with
Blanchett cast first and others the following year.
Principal photography began in April 2021 in Budapest, Hungary,
during the COVID-19 pandemic, and wrapped in June.
Two weeks of reshoots took place in early 2023, directed by Tim
Miller due to Roth's commitments to Thanksgiving.
That June, Mazin removed his name from the project
and was replaced by Joe Crombie.
Borderlands premiered at the TCL Chinese Theatre in Los Angeles, California on August 6,
2024, and was released in the United States by Lionsgate on August 9.
The film received negative reviews from critics and grossed $33
million against a budget of $110–120 million.
The film explores themes of outlaw, based on video game,
unlikely friendship, talking robot, malicious.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.